CARLOS YAHIR LARA RUIZ

Computer Science & Engineering Student



ABOUT ME

Student at the Universidad de Guadalajara, soon to graduate in december 2024. I have experience in web programming and development of functional applications. I am interested in learn more about AI and Cloud Systems.

Highly organized, committed to study and work. My professional goal is to develop and learn all the time in a great company, working as a team to achieve shared goals. I am constantly learning new technologies and improving my skills.

EXPERIENCE

Aug. 2022 - Mar. 2023

'Inventores Lab. -Universidad de Guadalajara'

Dr. David Bonilla 33 1134 4319

Feb. 2023 - Jul. 2023

'HEMAC Teleinformática'

Engr. Susana Vidrio 33 1601 1874

Laboratory coordinator

As a laboratory coordinator and project manager, I was involved in the development of web pages for the laboratory such as landing pages.

Also in the development of video games with Unity, Godot and Modeling projects in Blender and 3D printing.

Operations analysis

I supported projects of the 'Red Jalisco' program in the operations analysis department, where I documented and managed installation and maintenance documentation for multiple network devices and installations, Zapopan C5 cameras and video walls.

EDUCATION

2020 - Dec. 2024

Computer Engineering

Universidad de Guadalajara

Apr. 2024 - Now React and TypeScript Course UDEMY 2020 - 2022

B2 English Certification

Proulex UdeG

2018 - 2020

Diploma in Web Programming Universidad de Guadalajara

HARD SKILLS

- **JavaScript**
- Agile methodologies
- HTML/CSS
- C++
- Python
- Vite
- MySQL
- Git / GitHubVirtualBox
- React.js
- Linux
- Blender
- 3D Printing

SOFT SKILLS

Active Listening

3D modeling -

- Effective
- Proactive
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Autodidact
- Attention to detail
- Creativity

SOME PROJECTS

• Game made with Unity:

https://larz-12.itch.io/flappy-navi

• Landing page for Inventores Lab:

https://larz120.github.io/LandingPageInventores/index.html

CONTACT

Phone

+52 33 2009 3479

Email

carlosyahirlr@gmail.com

GitHub

github.com/larz120

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/carlos -yahir-lara-ruiz-b7b34a266